Be careful who you follow.
Influencer is a horror, thriller film directed by Kurtis David Harder.
While struggling on a solo backpacking trip in Thailand, social media influencer Madison
meets CW, who travels with ease and shows her a more uninhibited way of living.
But CW's interest in her takes a darker turn.
CW, played by Cassandra Naud.
Madison, played by Emily Tennant.
Ryan, played by Rory J. Saper.
Jessica, played by Sara Canning.
Rupert, played by Paul Spurrier.
Jay, played by Justin Sams.
Influencer is a 2022 American horror thriller film directed by Kurtis David
Harder from a screenplay he co-wrote with Tesh Guttikonda.
It stars Cassandra Naud, Emily Tennant, Rory J.
Saper and Sara Canning.
The film had its world premiere at the Brooklyn Horror Film Festival on
October 16, 2022 and was released on Shudder on May 26, 2023.
A sequel titled Influencers was released on Shudder in 2025.
The film explores themes of island, thailand, fake
identity, female protagonist, stolen identity.
The tone is dark and intense.